captain69.co.uk 2011-04-27

# Privacy policy

Privacy Policy...

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect _your_ privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way that your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, it is linked at the bottom of every page on the site so that it can be referred to whenever personally identifiable information may be requested.

For standard use of the site we do not collect any customer information apart from email addresses added when joining the site and when creating profiles. These are not required to be the same address and their usage is explained on the relevant pages where the information is entered. Members are also offered the opportunity to add contact details, web site addresses and social networking links when creating a profile. Apart from the initial email address which may be used for Email alerts (if requested) lost passwords or renewal reminders for annual subscribers, no other information is mandatory.

Please be aware that information added to a profile can be seen by other members of the site if you elect to add it to your viewable profile, forum posts, and message board postings.

Those members and advertisers who require invoices for accounting purposes will be asked to input their billing name (personal or company) and address.  Others may also wish to add their VAT Registration number.  This is all normal business practice and we give our unqualified assurance that such information is not viewable or available to any other member of the site.

View the [PayPoint](http://www.paypoint.net/information/privacy-policy/ "PayPoint Privacy Policy") Privacy Policy concerning collected information.
